mlmleads.com 2018-11-15

# MLM Leads Consultation - Call Today - (785) 539-6904

## MLM Leads General Privacy Policy

MLMLeads.com (MLMLeads) is committed to customer service and we intend to continue that tradition by providing a private and secure browsing experience at MLMLeads.com. The following policy will help you to understand how we will treat your personal information. As we continue to improve our site and as we take advantage of developments in technology, this policy may change from time to time so please check this policy on an ongoing basis for revisions and updates.

## PERSONAL INFORMATION:

We may collect personal information from users including (at minimum) first and last names, an email address to be used as a login, billing contact information, credit card number and a password. When a user registers online for our service, MLMLeads will take steps to validate the credit card and billing information supplied to us to ensure it is accurate. We also use this information to determine your eligibility for our one-time free trial offer. Your email address may be used to send you periodic product newsletters, offers and usage tips from MLMLeads. You can opt out of promotional emails at any time, but will still receive communications such as receipts, confirmation emails and customer service updates that are considered necessary to provide the service to you. We use the information collected to deliver services, process payments, update our records, communicate with you about products and services, and generally maintain your accounts with us. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active, as needed to provide you services, to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us at mlmleads.com. We do not share, sell, trade, or rent your personal information to third parties except as described in this privacy policy.

Information gathered at mlmleads.com is done so on a voluntary basis. You need not provide us with any personal information to use these sites. Information submitted on these sites can include contact information such as email addresses, comments on blog postings and job and press inquires. You should be aware that any information you provide in the comment or blog areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from these areas, please contact us at mlmleads.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

Because of our commitment to present the best possible product to all our users, we track the category of services selected by our individual users as well as all information pertaining to user satisfaction. To ensure the quality of our product, we reserve the right to maintain evaluation and feedback records.

## BUSINESS INFORMATION:

We will not view Business Information except as necessary to appropriately support the service or as required by law. (Business Information includes schedules, attendee lists, subject names, email addresses, names, session records, and any other business information used while in our software)

MLMLeads may store that information to fulfill our obligation to our customers, but we will not use the information to send marketing communications for third party offers to members. You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit while in session and utilizing the chat feature can be read, collected or used by the other member. Chat logs and meetings, and recordings are not stored or viewable by mlmleads.com and are only available locally to meeting organizers and attendees. We will not view business information, except as necessary to appropriately support the service and for the purpose of anticipating, diagnosing, supporting or resolving any problems that might limit or disrupt the quality of our customers� service experience or as required by law.

## PARTNERS:

In some cases we provide services or sell product lines jointly with other businesses. For these co-branded offerings in which a third party is involved in your transactions, we will sometimes share or jointly collect customer information related to those transactions with that third party. On any potential co-branded registration pages we will state who is collecting or receiving the information and whose privacy statement governs its use so that you will know at the time you create your account exactly how your information will be used. If you are registered with MLMLeads through a partnership and you request to opt out of receiving promotional updates, in order to comply with the provisions in the Can Spam Act, we will also provide your email address to that partner so that they may also discontinue sending you messages on behalf of mlmleads.com.

## AFFILIATES:

We may sometimes share or jointly collect information with our parent entity and the wholly owned subsidiaries and affiliated divisions of our parent company entity. Sharing this information helps us make your customer experience more seamless and efficient by allowing us to improve our marketing efforts to better target customer needs, streamline our processes and consolidate our backend business systems.

## SESSION RECORDS:

To maintain our quality of service and to assist in the analysis of product performance, we may also gather data on connection information, including the timing and size of all packets sent over the Internet during a session. The gathered information is used only to ensure the highest quality experience possible when using mlmleads services. SECURITY INFORMATION: MLMLeads also collects certain standard information about your computer for security and identification purposes. This information may include: IP addresses, domain names, access times, cookies and other unique identifying information of machines that have our software downloaded and installed on them. This information is used for the operation of the service, to identify and protect our customers and to control unauthorized use or abuse of our services. All information is encrypted during transmission and is stored securely within our servers.

## SURVEYS:

In addition to required member information, we may conduct surveys and ask users to volunteer demographic information to be used on an aggregate basis for internal market research, presentation to advertisers and joint research projects with outside companies involved in product development. We use such information to better focus our product and personalize the scope of services offered to each individual user.

## SOCIAL MEDIA:

Our Site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. These services will also authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. These Services may give you the option to post information about your activities on our websites to your profile page to share with others within your network. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.

## TESTIMONIALS:

With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us via one of the methods listed in this Privacy Policy.

## WEB ANALYTICS:

We continuously improve our websites and utilize different third party web analytic tools to help us do so. We are interested in how visitors use our websites, what they like and dislike, and where they have problems. We also use web analytical tools on our mobile applications to help gather non-personally identifiable data about download and application usage. In our use of web analytics we do not collect GeoLocation data. We may use information such as IP addresses to determine the general geographic locations areas of our visitors, but this information is not correlated to personal information about individual users. The web beacons used in connection with our web analytics services do not share any personally identifiable information about our website and application visitors with third parties. These tools may gather data such as what browser a person uses, what operating systems are used, what is downloaded, and what content, products and services are reviewed when visiting or registering for services at one of our websites or mobile applications. This information is used solely to assist mlmleads.com in maintaining a more effective and useful website for our customers.

We track aggregate traffic patterns throughout our site but we do not correlate this information with personally identifiable data about individual users. We track domain names, browser types and MIME type. Such information will not be passed to third parties without your prior consent unless where required by applicable law.

## COOKIES:

A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. We use cookies to track user traffic patterns and hold certain registration information. When you register at mlmleads.com sites, we use cookies to store unique, randomly assigned user IDs that we generate for administrative purposes. These cookies enable you to enter the mlmleads.com site without having to log on each time. We do not store passwords or any Personal Information about you in the cookies.

Local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, may be used by third parties for some of our product training videos. These cookies are used to store preferences for the videos such as volume control. Flash cookies are not used to back-up, recreate or re-spawn a browser cookie that a user may delete. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and way data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies.

If you wish to not have the information these technologies collect used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by sending us an email to support @ mlmleads.com. The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. You can still review the website if you choose to set your browser to refuse all cookies; however, you must enable cookies in order to establish an account and to download and install any of the software.

+=+=+=+=+= 

## MLMLeads.com Mobile Marketing Privacy Policy

What information do we collect? We collect information in two ways:

  1. When you give it to us or give us permission to obtain it. When you sign up for or use our products, you voluntarily give us certain information. This can include your name, profile photo, social posts, comments, likes, email address you used to sign up, and any other information you provide us. If you�re using MLMLeads on your mobile device, you can also choose to provide us with location data. You also may give us permission to access your information in other services. For example, you may link your Facebook or Twitter account to MLMLeads, which allows us to obtain information from those accounts (e.g., your friends or contacts). The information we obtain from those services often depends on your settings or their privacy policies, so be sure to check what those are.
  2. We also get technical information when you use our products or use websites or apps that have MLMLeads features. These days, whenever you use a website, mobile application, or other Internet service, there�s certain information that almost always gets created and recorded automatically. The same is true when you use our products. Here are some of the types of information we collect:  

    * � Log Data. When you use MLMLeads or go to a webpage or use an app that has MLMLeads features, our servers automatically record information (�log data�) including information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website or your mobile app sends when you�re using it. This log data may include your Internet Protocol address, the address of the web pages you visited that had MLMLeads features, browser type and settings, the date and time of your request, how you used MLMLeads, and cookie data. 
    * � Cookie data. Depending on how you�re accessing our products, we may use �cookies� (a small text file sent by your computer each time you visit our website, unique to your MLMLeads account or your browser), or similar technologies to record log data. When we use cookies, we may use �session� cookies (that last until you close your browser) or �persistent� cookies (that last until you or your browser delete them). For example, we may use cookies to store your language preferences or other MLMLeads settings so you don�t have to set them up every time you visit MLMLeads. Some of the cookies we use are associated with your MLMLeads account (including personal information about you, such as the email address you gave us), and other cookies are not. 
    * � Device Information. In addition to log data, we may also collect information about the device you�re using MLMLeads on, including what type of device it is, what operating system you�re using, device settings, unique device identifiers, and crash data. Whether we collect some or all of this information often depends on what type of device you�re using and its settings. For example, different types of information are available depending on whether you�re using a Mac or a PC, or an iPhone or an Android phone. To learn more about what information your device makes available to us, please also check the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider.   

How do we use the information we collect? 

We use the information we collect to provide our products to you and make them better, develop new products, and protect MLMLeads and our users. For example, we may log how often people use two different versions of a product, which can help us understand which version is better. 

We also use the information we collect to offer you customized content, including: 

    * Suggesting content you might like. For example, if you�ve indicated that you�re interested in make money from home and has MLMLeads has those features, we may suggest related content, or people that we think you might like; 
    * Showing you ads you might be interested in. Learn more about how we use information from outside of MLMLeads to customize your MLMLeads experience. We also use the information we collect to: 
    * Send you updates (such as when certain activity, like comments, news alerts), newsletters, marketing materials and other information that may be of interest to you. For example, depending on your email notification settings, we may send you weekly updates that include content you may like. You can decide to stop getting these updates by updating your account settings (or through other settings we may provide). 
    * Help your friends and contacts find you. For example, if you sign up using a Facebook account, we may help your Facebook friends find your account on MLMLeads. 
    * Respond to your questions or comments. 

The information we collect may be �personally identifiable� (meaning it can be used to specifically identify you as a unique person) or �non-personally identifiable� (meaning it can�t be used to specifically identify you). We use both types of information, and combinations of both types, as described above. We may use or store information wherever MLMLeads does business, including countries outside your own. 

    * What choices do you have about your information? 

Our goal is to give you simple and meaningful choices over your information. If you have a MLMLeads account, many of the choices you have on MLMLeads are built directly in to the product or your account settings. For example, you can: 

    * Access and change information in your social profiles at any time, choose whether your profile page is available to search engines;   

    * Link or unlink your MLMLeads account from an account on another service (e.g., Facebook or Twitter). For some services (like Facebook), you can also choose whether or not to publish your activity to that service.   

    * Close your account at any time. When you close your account, we�ll deactivate it and remove your content from MLMLeads. We may retain archived copies of your information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes (including to help address fraud and spam).   

In addition to the examples above, you may have choices available to you through the device or software you use to access MLMLeads. 

For example: The browser you use may provide you with the ability to control cookies or other types of local data storage. 

Your mobile device may provide you with choices around how and whether location or other data is shared with us. 

To learn more about these choices, please see the information provided by the device or software provider. 

How do we share the information we collect? MLMLeads is a marketing tool.

    * When you create content in your MLMLeads account, anyone can view them. You may also provide us with profile information that that anyone can view. The other limited instances where we may share your personal information include: 
    * When we have your consent. This includes sharing information with other services (like Facebook or Twitter) when you�ve chosen to link to your MLMLeads account to those services or publish your activity on MLMLeads to them. For example, you can choose to publish your content to Facebook or Twitter. 
    * We may employ third party companies or individuals to process personal information on our behalf based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy. For example, we may share data with a security consultant to help us get better at identifying spam or with our accountants to make sure we�re keeping the books right. In addition, some of the information we request may be collected by third party providers on our behalf. 
    * If we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety, rights, or property of the public, any person, or MLMLeads; or to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues. 
    * We may engage in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, or similar transaction or proceeding that involves the transfer of the information described in this Policy.   

We may also share aggregated or non-personally identifiable information with our partners or others. For example, we may tell a business using MLMLeads how content is being shared, or the percentage of people who click on content after viewing it. 

Our Policy on Children�s Information 

MLMLeads is not directed to children under 13. If you learn that your minor child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us. 

How do we make changes to this policy? 

We may change this policy from time to time, and if we do we�ll post any changes on this page. If you continue to use MLMLeads after those changes are in effect, you agree to the revised policy. If the changes are significant, we may provide more prominent notice or obtain your consent as required by law.
